$SSER_INSTALLSSTRIPPERDONE_NOTIFY{}	SerialStripper {} installed.
$SSER_STRIPONKEYPRESS	Strip on keypress
$SSER_STRIPONKEYPRESS_DESC	ON: will strip when key is pressed\nOFF: key inactive.
$SSER_KEYFORSTRIPPING	Key for stripping
$SSER_KEYFORSTRIPPING_DESC	Select the key for stripping.
$SSER_KEYCONFLICTWITHVANILLA{}	This key is already mapped to:\n{}\n\nAre you sure you want to continue?
$SSER_YES	Yes
$SSER_NO	No
$SSER_KEYCONFLICTWITHMOD{}{}	This key is already mapped to:\n{}\n({})\n\nAre you sure you want to continue?
$SSER_KEYPRESSDURATIONFORFULLSTRIP	Keypress duration for full strip
$SSER_KEYPRESSDURATIONFORFULLSTRIP_DESC	Select how long the key should be held to start a full serial strip.\nSimple taps will trigger a single serial strip.
$SSER_TIMEBETWEENANIMANDSTRIP	Time between anim & strip
$SSER_TIMEBETWEENANIMANDSTRIP_DESC	After a stripping animation ends, this defines how long to wait until the items are stripped\nAdjust according to your system's speed to achieve best results.

$SSER_UNINSTALLSSTRIPPER	Uninstall SerialStripper only
$SSER_UNINSTALLSSTRIPPERCONFIRM_MSG	This will uninstall SerialStripper only.\nSerialStrip will not be uninstalled.\nProceed?
$SSER_UNINSTALLSSTRIPPERANDSSTRIPCONFIRM_MSG	This will uninstall SerialStripper AND SerialStrip.\nProceed?
$SSER_UNINSTALLSSTRIPPERDONE_MSG	SerialStripper has been uninstalled. Please save your game and remove the mod.
$SSER_UNINSTALLSSTRIPPERANDSSTRIP	Uninstall SerialStripper & SerialStrip
$SSER_UNINSTALLSSTRIPPER_DESC	This will remove any values and arrays that SerialStripper may have created, so that it can be uninstalled safely without leaving stuff in the savegame.\nAfter this, save the game and remove the mod.
$SSER_UNINSTALLSSTRIPPERANDSSTRIP_DESC	This will remove any values and arrays that SerialStripper & SerialStrip may have created, so that they can be uninstalled safely without leaving stuff in the savegame.\nAfter this, save the game and remove both mods.
$SSER_UNINSTALLSSTRIPPERANDSSTRIPDONE_MSG	SerialStripper and SerialStrip have been uninstalled. Please save your game and remove these mods.