$STRIP_ON_KEYPRESS	Strip on keypress
$KEY_FOR_STRIPPING	Key for stripping
$KEYPRESS_DURATION_FOR_FULL_STRIP	Keypress duration for full strip
$TIME_BETWEEN_ANIM_&_STRIP	Time between anim & strip
$EXPLAIN_StripKeyOnOff	ON: will strip when key is pressed\nOFF: key inactive.
$EXPLAIN_StripKey	Select the key for stripping.
$KEY_CONFLICT_WITH_MOD{}{}	This key is already mapped to:\n{}\n({})\n\nAre you sure you want to continue?
$KEY_CONFLICT_WITH_VANILLA{}	This key is already mapped to:\n{}\n\nAre you sure you want to continue?
$YES	Yes
$NO	No
$EXPLAIN_HoldTimeForFullStrip	Select how long the key should be held to start a full serial strip.\nSimple taps will trigger a single serial strip.
$EXPLAIN_WaitingTimeAfterAnim	After a stripping animation ends, this defines how long to wait until the items are stripped\nAdjust according to your system's speed to achieve best results.